Wow!
I've really slimmed down, don'tcha think?
French Fry Odyssey
Looks like you're making great progress!
Yup! I've been working my butt off lately.
So does that mean you're
heading home again?
Sure am. I make sure to visit
every once in a while.
Elfuda's family...
I wonder what they're like...
Elfuda?
Human... I've been killing it
with the weight loss lately, right?
Don'tcha think I deserve a little reward
for all my hard work?
I guess you've got a point...
Alright, you can buy some fries.
R-really?!
But stick to one small serving.
You'll spoil your dinner.
What are you, my mother?
Congratulations!
Satero
O-on what?
You're our location's 10,000th customer!
And to celebrate, we're gifting you
a year's supply of free French fries!
A year's supply?!
Here's your stack of coupons!
I'm the King of the Fries!
Are you kidding me?!
Let's put 'em to use!
Ten orders of fries!
No! Don't do it!
Potatoes of Shame and the Titan's Fist
The door was open so we let ourselves in!
Been a while, hasn't it?
Y'know, I was thinking we oughtta
switch up the bodyguard schedule so that-
What a surprise.
Wasn't expecting visitors.
Potatopia
J-jeez, did you gain more...
Wait, wh-where's the human?
Oh, hey there.
What the...?!
Where in the hell did these
bowling ball bellies come from?!
Knock it off! My clothes are gonna
fall apart if you shake me too hard!
Human! Ignore them and eat your fries!
M'kay!
Nom, nom... Munch, munch...
Quit gorging yourself!
It's faint, but there are
traces of magic on those fries...
Oh no... The satyr?!
But we haven't seen her
since the last time.
Still, I can't think of anyone else
who'd do this.
Tricking you is one thing,
but manipulating the human
is no small feat.
Did anything weird happen?
Hmm...
Well, not unless you count winning
a year's supply of free French fries...
That doesn't strike you as weird?!
It's a magic spell known as a "charm."
It messes with your head
and impairs your judgment.
Probably explains why you and
the elf stuffed your faces
without noticing anything was wrong.
No wonder I felt like the fries
were tastier than normal...
Wait, she also charmed Elfuda?
That fat tub of lard has a resistance
to magic, so not even close.
This was just her usual
greed for French fries.
Staaaaare...
Speak of the devil. We got company.
I hadn't counted on the elf
being immune to my sorcery...
But this works for me.
We meet again, you idiotic elf!
The burger lady?
Oopsies, I forgot to deactivate my disguise.
It's you...
The satyr!
All according to plan! You're looking
awfully chunky, you nasty elf!
Hey, who're you calling nasty?!
Oh please, I know you haven't forgotten
what you did to humiliate me!
Nooooo!
You stripped me naked and stood by
while that man leered at me!
I did absolutely nothing of the sort!
So I vowed to get my revenge
for your despicable behavior!
I swear!
So I vowed to get my revenge
for your despicable behavior!
I would never!
So I vowed to get my revenge
for your despicable behavior!
Oh, come on! How am I supposed to
defend myself against that?!
But if you were the only one given fries,
the human would've put a stop to it...
That's the reason you
fattened up the human too!
You catch on quick.
Great, you got your revenge.
I'd rather not waste mana on
a pointless fight, so please leave.
Hmph!
My plot for revenge doesn't stop at
fattening the two of them up.
No, it goes much deeper than that...
H-huh?
She's attempting to feed off
the human's avarice?!
Not happening! Ya snooze, ya lose!
...and it comes to fruition as soon as
the elf races to save him.
I call it "Operation Bloat Her Belly
and Tear Her Clothes to Shreds
When She Moves Too Fast!
Plus a Nip Slip!"
Now you're going to suffer
the same humiliation I did!
And that was my goal all along!
Y'see, isn't it embarrassing?!
A man gawking at your birthday suit!
How does it feel?!
Eh, it doesn't really bother me.
Huh?
Yeah, he manhandles me all the time.
Wait, wh-what...?!
You m-m-manhandle each other
while naked on a regular basis?!
Not like that!
She meant a massage! A massage!
I-it's over...
I'm out of my depth...
Listen, it wasn't-
It's hopeless... I'm doomed...
Just kill me!
Can you let me talk for a second?!
Not much of a conclusion...
Kinda underwhelming.
Agreed.
Had I known, I would've taken a shift
at the corner store instead...
Looks like WE won! Right, human?
Ouch! Please cover yourself up!
C'mon, no need to be shy!
Hey, cut it out!
Why would you smack me
on the shoulder?!
That's how your clothes fell apart!
M-my bad...
Nooooo!
Maybe she finally learned her lesson.
Great. Now get dressed, wouldja?
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
Hours of Operation
One, two! One, two!
Okay, let's take a short break.
Whew, I'm beat!
Oink...
Man, this sucks...
Don't forget to stay hydrated, ladies.
Star Spud
Huh, didn't know the boss owns a gym.
Yeah. She opened the place up
about six months ago.
An overachiever, eh?
But why a boxing gym?
Well, uh...
Young men glistening with sweat
as they pour their hearts and souls
into their physical fitness...
Their tight, succulent bodies...
Who wouldn't wanna see that up close?!
...is what she said.
Your boss sure is something...
Still, I'm grateful that she lets me
use it on days when it's normally closed.
That's how I got into shape.
It might be a good opportunity for you too.
Opportunity...?
I was thinking I'd have you ladies
give some different sports a try.
Having fun while staying active
is always a plus.
It's easier to turn exercising
into a habit if we enjoy it!
That's right.
Now then, how about we do
some light sparring next?
Sparring?
It's a fish!
Incorrect!
It's a form of training where you
don't actually hit your opponent.
We're bound to have an accident if we
pit two beginners against each other,
so you'll be facing me.
We'll aim to rotate out every two minutes.
'Kay, Elfuda. You're up first.
S-sure!
Alrighty, the clock's a-tickin'!
Remember your combos!
Eyes on your opponent,
and stay light on your feet!
Never, ever let your guard down!
This stuff takes a lot of energy...
I thought two minutes would be
a breeze, but this sucks!
Huh?!
Rumble
So... it's my turn now, right?
Hey, no pummeling the human!
You'll knock his head clean off!
I know, I know.
Here goes!
Take this!
O-Oga?!
Aw, just kidding!
I can't do it... I'm too afraid
of getting punched!
Seriously?
Then somebody else spar with me.
Nope, no siree! I don't want my face
rearranged into modern art!
I'm too young to die!
Sparring is off the table!
You're a liability!
Fine, whatever...
I'm used to being a big old misfit...
I'm sorry, Oga.
It's the difference in strength and size...
Huh...?
Where are all the trainers...?
Hello.
She's even bigger than Oga...
Um, the gym's technically closed today.
It's closed? Oh shoot.
Guess I got the schedule mixed up!
That's kinda embarrassing...
The people behind you are...
Oh! Th-that's just...
W-we're in the middle of inventing
a brand new sport called "costume boxing"!
Calm down, human.
There's no need for us to hide.
What?
Look closely at her.
She's a...
Of all the places to run into an elf...
Color me surprised!
A cyclops!
That's me.
She's got... one eye?!
Indeed. They're a race of one-eyed giants.
You guys like boxing too?
Well, we're takin' a stab at it!
How long have you been
boxing, Miss Cyclops?
About a month or so.
But I've never sparred with anyone
on account of being really big
and scaring people away.
It's because you giant types
are uncannily strong.
My name's Naoe. And you are...?
Hitome.
Well, Hitome, you don't have
an opponent to spar with, right?
Sure don't.
In that case, would you consider
sparring with our friend Oga here?
Huh?
You have a similar build,
so I think it'd be a perfect match!
Better quit while you're ahead, human.
Yup, she's right.
But why?
Ogres are giants too.
The giant races like fightin' for dominance
and they hate losin'.
It's in their blood!
Our folklore contains many gruesome tales
born of their competitive nature.
W-wait, really?
B-but it might be too late to stop them...!
Huh?!
R-remember, ladies!
It's LIGHT sparring!
That means no actual contact, okay?!
Yeah, yeah.
Sundome style.
Hya!
Seriously?!
Weak sauce!
I told them not to hit each other!
Stop, stop!
That's enough, you two!
It's no use.
They're not listening to me...
Let it go, human.
They won't stop until they're satisfied.
"Enjoying a sport while also staying active."
They're doing what you
told them to do, aren't they?
This isn't what I had in mind...